zaneyclicks.com 2019-07-21

# Zaney Clicks

(Updated 6/24/2019)  

By registering for Zaney Clicks you agree that you have read these terms, understand them, and agree to be bound by them.  

Unless you received prior permission from Zaney Clicks, you may only register for one Zaney Clicks account.I agree that I will be using a email address that does NOT lead to a non-existent email account or a catch all account that will fill up and bounce emails. I further understand that I should emails sent to me bounce I accept I will likely have my account suspended and lose any Income that I may have earned. As part of our terms of service, you have agreed to receive our e-mails. Any bounced emails will cause the immediate suspension of your account.  

**Anyone that is caught cheating by using a bot will be suspended, banned and all earnings will be put back in the site for** Zaney Clicks **to pay honest members**.  

If you signup with a fake email address and it keeps bouncing, then I have no choice but to suspend your account. I am not unreasonable here but when you join a site, you agree to get the sites emails - how else will you know what is going on, upcoming promos, new features, etc.  

You may not promote Zaney Clicks in a way that could be considered spamming. You may only promote your referral URL and/or other promotional material in other surf sites or advertising programs that allow it. Promoting Zaney Clicks in a way that could be considered spamming will result in removal of your Zaney Clicks account and possible legal action.  

It is okay with me if the Administrators of Zaney Clicks send me email if they have news or something they feel is worth my consideration. I understand that the Administrators will not abuse this and emails will be kept to a minimum. If they send to many, I will request a payout and quit the program.  

Users are completely responsible for the content they promote using Zaney Clicks. Users are responsible for ensuring they have the rights to promote a URL, and any content it contains. Zaney Clicks is not responsible if a user is in violation of another legal agreement, copyright infringement, or any other issues.  

**OUR CASH POLICY**

Payout for members is $25.00.

You can request a payout by sending in a support ticket

Commissions paid out to FREE members will **NOT** include any Cash Prizes received, only commissions from referral sales of upgrades and credit sales.   

**If the name in your payment processor account does not match your name at this site - you will be suspended.   **

NOTE ! Free Members can use your commissions to upgrade and when you reach the 25.00  
payout - you will be paid.

Payouts can take up to 10 days to receive as I do my own admin work.

Once you have qualified members May Request A Cash out Once You Have At Least $25.00 In Your Account. (please read above before requesting on how to qualify)  

**REFUND POLICY**

Zaney Clicks provides a digital advertising product and service. Due to the nature of the product and service there will be NO REFUNDS provided. Zaney Clicks does not guarantee results from using our product as this is solely the responsibility of the user.

Zaney Clicks is in no way associated with any payment processor and merely uses them to process payments for advertising purchases.

Furthermore, Zaney Clicks will not be held responsible or liable for any problems, damages, or losses that may occur with regard to a member's direct association with any payment processor and any other aspects of their account. If any member cancels their Zaney Clicks account, that member will be responsible for cancelling any subscriptions member may have with Zaney Clicks through the payment processor source

. Member MUST go to the payment processor and cancel the subscription otherwise the monthly fees will continue. YOUR Payment Processor account is YOUR responsibility!

Zaney Clicks will not issue any refunds for credits purchased or for failure to cancel services. Subscribed members must login monthly to receive the monthly credit allotment which comes with the subscription.

Your relationship to Zaney Clicks is one of an independent contractor and/or customer. No employee-employer relationship is created by your use of the Service. You do not have any obligation to refer new members to the Zaney Clicks Program. Zaney Clicks HAS NO OBLIGATION TO OFFER THE SERVICE OR OTHER PROMOTIONS TO YOU.

**URL Rules**

Before submitting a URL to Zaney Clicks, please read these rules very carefully and make sure your URL does not violate any of them. If you violate any of these rules, your site will be deleted along with any credits assigned to them. Your Zaney Clicks account may also be deleted.  

*No sites with illegal activity.

*No pyramid or ponzi schemes

*No matrix or get-rich programs

*No frame-breaking sites.

*No viruses, trojans, or spyware.

*No adult content.

*Rotators may be promoted only if all sites or banners in rotation comply with these terms.

*No HYIPs or "investment autosurfs". These are illegal in most countries, including the United States.

*No PTP sites.  

*Sites with multiple popups and popunders or other frame stopping or irritating gadgets will be removed without warning and banned from the system.  

*Zaney Clicks has the full right to delete any site that is inappropriate or questionable.  

**If you do not know how to add sites, banners or text ad site, then contact me - I will be very happy to help you as I know what it is like to be a newbie - I have been there.

**Privacy Statement**

**THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT DISCLOSES THE PRIVACY PRACTICES FOR ZANEY CLICKS**

**Information Collection and Use of Information**  
In order to use this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give his contact information (email address). This information is used to contact the user about the service and products we provide or wish to provide. **We will not sell, share, or rent personal information to others.**

**Security**  
This website takes every precaution to protect our users personal information. When a user submits sensitive information via our site, the information is protected both online and off-line. Only the administrator of this site can access personal information of the users.

**Correction/Updating Personal Information**  
If a user's personally identifiable information changes, we provide a way to correct that user's personal data provided to us. This can be done within the member area in your profile.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.  

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.  

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.  

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to disable/decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.  

**Right to Cancel**  
Our users can cancel membership and be removed from all newsletters and databases. To do this a member can go to their profile and unclick to receive newsletters.  You can also delete your account at anytime from your profile page.

**Site and Service Updates**  
We may send the user site and service announcement updates. We communicate with the users to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their accounts via email.

**Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our Privacy Policy we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner.

**It is MY responsibility to check out these terms from time to time as they may change without notification.**
